(Penny:)-No.
-All right.
(Leonard:)Raj and Howard
are at Howard's moms,
(Leonard:)but should we call the girls
and see if they want to come?
(Penny:)-No. Bernadette's working late.
-Amy's sick.
(Leonard:)-What's wrong with her?
-Well, she talks a lot.
(Sheldon:)She always wants to hold hands.
(Leonard:)That's not what I meant.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you were
referring to her illness,
(Sheldon:)your question should have been,
"What ails her?"
(Sheldon:)-What ails her?
-Oh. Who knows?
(Penny:)Come on, anything can happen.
We can push him down the stairs!
(Howard:)Hey. Thanks for coming to hang out.
(Raj:)No problem. How's your mom feeling?
(Howard:)Okay, but she'd feel better
if she took her medicine.
(Raj:)You know, when Cinnamon
won't take her medicine,
(Raj:)I hide it in a piece of cheese.
(Howard:)Good idea.
We can wrap the pill in cheese,
(Howard:)feed it to Cinnamon,
and then my mom can eat Cinnamon.
(Howard:)-What do you feel like doing?
-I was thinking we could watch a DVD.
(Howard:)Well, my mom doesn't have
a lot to choose from.
(Howard:)Unless you want to watch
the video of her colonoscopy.